Guide to the Reboot records M2095
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Reboot records
circa 2002-2007
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Henry Hollander, Bookseller
Reboot
M2095
0.6 Linear Feet (2 boxes)
Biographical / Historical Note
Reboot is a non-profit organization headquartered in New York focused on Jewish-American arts and (counter) culture, with the mission of affirming "the value of Jewish traditions and creat[ing] new ways for people to make them their own." Founded in 2002, it has hub communities in San Francisco and Los Angeles, among other places.
Content Description
The materials consist of Reboot board meeting minutes, periodical issues, handbills, promotional materials, financial records, and other documents.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection was given to Stanford University by Henry Hollander, Bookseller, in 2015.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Note that material must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use.
Jews -- United States -- Societies, etc.; Henry Hollander, Bookseller; Reboot
- Board meeting: July 12th and 13th, 2004, Santa Monica, CA (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
- Miscellaneous material from the binder (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Board meeting: December 15th and 16th, 2004, Santa Monica, CA (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Board meeting: January 18th and 19th, 2006, San Francisco, CA (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
- Board meeting: July 245h and 25th, 2006, New York, NY (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
- Miscellaneous material from the binder (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Promotional material (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Board meeting: October 4th and 5th, 2007, Los Angeles, CA (Half-box 2, Folder 1)
- Microgrants, 2002-2003 (Half-box 2, Folder 2)
- Accounting: invoices 2002/2003; FJC financials; grant assistance reports (Half-box 2, Folder 3-4)